<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Fiction on Aiwayi Arca</title><link>https://arcapol.github.io/tags/fiction/</link><description>Recent content in Fiction on Aiwayi Arca</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.150.0</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:53:58 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://arcapol.github.io/tags/fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Short Bath</title><link>https://arcapol.github.io/posts/short-bath/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:53:58 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://arcapol.github.io/posts/short-bath/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Come on we are going to be late, I do not want to let go of my bath time&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the best day of the year. With temperatures crossing 50 degrees in the heat of Delhi, today&amp;rsquo;s bath will be a relief. It has been 5 years now that Indians have started conserving water to this extent. The progress has been astonishing. Water globally has depleted to such an extent that water is now rationed based on family needs. This is the first crisis in which the world came together under the ambit of UNO to take actions to prevent further depletion. While the governments over the world are working hard to increase the supply of fresh water, it has not led to any fruitful results given the global warming and the annhilation of the Arctic by the Russians.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Evaporate</title><link>https://arcapol.github.io/posts/evaporate/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:58:07 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://arcapol.github.io/posts/evaporate/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;“It is over, you should move on”. The words still ring in my ears. I hear it in the cacophony of a wedding, I hear it in the silence of night, I hear it waking up, I hear it laying down. There were a hundred lines left to say, a thousand moments to look upon and her words tore apart a movie which could have been.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hi, How are you?”, said an uncle. Who he is I am not sure, why is he talking to me, no idea. “Namaste, how are you?”. These days I use &lt;em&gt;Namaste&lt;/em&gt; as a catchall phrase. I don’t have to know anyone and I can do that without disrespecting them. I do not remember what happened afterwards, what we spoke about, if we spoke.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>