<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Aiwayi Arca</title><link>https://arcapol.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Aiwayi Arca</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:53:58 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://arcapol.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Short Bath</title><link>https://arcapol.github.io/posts/short-bath/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:53:58 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://arcapol.github.io/posts/short-bath/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Come on we are going to be late, I do not want to let go of my bath time&amp;rdquo;
This is the best day of the year. With temperatures crossing 50 degrees in the heat of Delhi, today&amp;rsquo;s bath will be a relief. It has been 5 years now that Indians have started conserving water to this extent. The progress has been astonishing. Water globally has depleted to such an extent that water is now rationed based on family needs.</description></item><item><title>Evaporate</title><link>https://arcapol.github.io/posts/evaporate/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:58:07 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://arcapol.github.io/posts/evaporate/</guid><description>“It is over, you should move on”. The words still ring in my ears. I hear it in the cacophony of a wedding, I hear it in the silence of night, I hear it waking up, I hear it laying down. There were a hundred lines left to say, a thousand moments to look upon and her words tore apart a movie which could have been.
“Hi, How are you?”, said an uncle.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://arcapol.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:08:51 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://arcapol.github.io/about/</guid><description>I have always been afraid of writing. I always regard authors with high respect. The articles or books they write are well researched and thought out and the writing flows as a conversation into the reader’s mind.
My writing does not match, unfortunately, any of the qualities mentioned above. Nevertheless, I plan to start writing not as a way to impart wisdom, but to document my imperfections and work on it.</description></item></channel></rss>